Nice work.
You made it to the end of this module.
How are you feeling?
Over the past few videos,
I've taken you through the many facets
of team management and influencing.
You learned to explain the importance of
teamwork in creating a high-functioning team
that can complete
the work of a project on time.
And you learned how to lead in ways that
motivate others to succeed, both at
the team level and
on an individual level too.
You learned about the 5 stages of team
development, which is a helpful framework
for understanding and managing
sometimes challenging team dynamics.
I explained how to apply techniques for
effectively influencing the people
around you, and you learned what not to
do when trying to influence others.
And finally, you learned about the sources
of power, both organizational and
personal that contribute to your
overall ability to influence your team.
Coming up, I'll take you through
effective project communication.
See you soon